<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>While You're Up - Performance Fix</name>
  <packageId>fluxxfield.whileyoureup.perffix</packageId>
  <author>CodeOptimist (original), cslaneyflett (1.6 port), FluxxField (performance fix)</author>
  <url>https://github.com/FluxxField/rimworld-while-youre-up-perf-fix</url>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.6</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <modDependencies>
    <li>
      <packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
      <displayName>Harmony</displayName>
      <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
      <downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
    </li>
  </modDependencies>
  <incompatibleWith>
    <li>hoodie.whileyoureup</li>
    <li>kevlou127.WhileHYouOreHUpHQ1V0S</li>
    <li>CodeOptimist.JobsOfOpportunity</li>
    <li>zsbk.patch16.whileyoureup</li>
  </incompatibleWith>
  <loadBefore/>
  <loadAfter/>
  <description><![CDATA[<b>Performance-fixed fork of While You're Up (1.6 patch).</b>

This is a fork of cslaneyflett's 1.6 port of CodeOptimist's While You're Up, with critical performance fixes identified by ModScope: Profiler.

<color=teal><b>Performance Fixes:</b></color>
- Fixed 4 cache invalidation bugs that cleared the storage cell cache on every tick, causing full map-wide storage searches for every item in every pawn's inventory every tick
- Added global shared storage cache across all pawns — when one colonist finds where steel goes, all other colonists reuse the answer instantly
- Storage cache automatically invalidates when storage zones change
- Replaced 5 per-tick Traverse reflection calls with cached FieldInfo/PropertyInfo/MethodInfo lookups
- Eliminated duplicate Linq pass over inventory items (two GetDefHaul passes → one)
- Replaced Linq Intersect+Contains with direct Contains check

Original cost: ~20ms/tick. Fixed cost: less than 0.5ms/tick.

<color=teal><b>Original Features:</b></color>
Opportunistic hauling. Haul-to-inventory improvements (only if Pick Up And Haul is installed).

A must-have with PUAH. Compatible with existing saves. Any load order.

<b>Use this mod INSTEAD of the original While You're Up (1.6 patch), not alongside it.</b>

AGPL-3.0 licensed. Original mod by CodeOptimist, 1.6 port by cslaneyflett.
]]></description>
</ModMetaData>
